[{"answer": "On what he missed.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 8, "question": "But sometimes if it wasn't for the strap, what would this world be like today?", "qSentId": 7}, {"answer": "I always thought about that, but Michael seemed happy.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "Did you ever hope that he would find true love?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "He's about 9 or 10 there.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "What I'm struck by, I love this picture, Katherine which is -- how old is he there, Michael?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "He taught himself.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Did he teach himself?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Was he always painting secretly without people really being aware of it?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "A bit of escape, is it?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Well, I have -- we have 98 pieces.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "And this collection, how many pieces are there in it?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "He just had an obsession of chairs.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Why did he like drawing or painting chairs?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Are they showing it on?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, to a certain extent.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "I mean if you had your time again, would you want the kids, especially Michael, to go into that crazy world?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "ACKSON: I didn't think he was too tough, but in -- back in those days everybody raised their children about the same.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Did he -- did he have to be that tough?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "I think it's gone a bit too soft.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Do you think that the world has gone a bit soft in terms of discipline?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "The bible tells us the world will be destroyed.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "Well, I think society is sometimes is the fault of it.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "When you look at America, modern America now, where do you think people are going wrong especially in bringing up children?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "I mean it's interesting.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "What are the parents to do?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "How did you feel as his mother?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Just hold that thought for a moment, Katherine.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Why are they doing this to him?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "I've talked to him about it.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "The rest of the world may not see this in the innocent way that you do?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "You know what, I think a lot of that was exaggerated about the different things that he was taking.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "I mean do you think that all the drugs he was taking for the anxiety, for the lack of sleep, the painkillers and so on, was it all connected, do you think, in the end to the pressure that he felt and the tension and the stress?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "What do you think, as his mother, caused his death?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Never met him.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Did you ever meet Conrad Murray?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Has he ever tried to contact you?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "He's never written to you or anything?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Will you ever get over this, Katherine, do you think?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "I just miss him.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "What do you think when you think of him?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "It's so unnatural, isn't it?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "You know, we have a trial going on and I'd rather not say.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "How did you think he was in the buildup to his death physically?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Were you concerned about him?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Do you feel that there were bad people around him?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "It was all about money, you think?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "They're getting along very well.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "How are they getting along?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "His grades are so good.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Is he?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Do you see the spirit of Michael in them?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Yes, Paris does.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "If they want to go into show business?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Well, I'm pleased and I'm concerned at the same time because I didn't -- I don't think that Michael would wanted her to be out there this soon.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Do you feel pleased about that or concerned?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "She's very good.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "I mean how talented are they?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "You know, I don't think that they act like normal children.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "How do you think they have coped with losing their father?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Well, his enthusiasm to succeed brought all the strength out in him.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Were you concerned about him as a friend?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Well, during the time that he was pretty much studying to do these concerts, I had very little contact with him.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Were you concerned as a friend of his about what was possibly going on?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "I know he'll be remembered as the artist he was.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Katherine, what would you like Michael's legacy to be?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Starving young children with the big bellies.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "You mean the scenes from Ethiopia and places in Africa with the starving young children?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "The things that were coming out, the things that media -- and most people believe what they hear and what they read.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "What do you think is the biggest misconception about Michael for people who didn't know him?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Like they were saying he was molesting young boys and other things that he was doing, that he might have been on painkillers, things like that.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "No way.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Do you think it is even remotely possibly that he could have done anything inappropriate with a young boy?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "You know, Michael, he was one of my younger children.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Is that how you felt?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "No, not really.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "Did that scare you, that level of fame?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "I talked to him at least twice a month and sometimes more.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "How often would you talk to him?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Did you feel you had a very close relationship?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Yes, he did.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Do you feel he confided in you?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "You know, I always thought about that, but Michael seemed happy.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Did you ever hope that he would find true love?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I -- I did.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Did you feel that?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Yes, he played most of the things he had.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Would he try stuff out with you?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "If you said Michael, I don't really like that one, would he drop it?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "\"Man In The Mirror.\"", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "What was your favorite of all his songs?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "That's one of my favorites.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Well, it was a message of greatness.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Why \"Man In The Mirror\"?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "I felt he was happy.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Was Michael happy in the end, do you think?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "It's good to hear.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "That's good to hear, isn't it?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "It made me feel good.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Well, Michael spent a good part of 25 years making this art.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "One is what are you going to do with this art?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Well, Michael always wanted to exhibit his art.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "And they're going to want to know if they can get ahold them?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Michael and I went around that monument.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "It's based on the Prince Albert Monument in London?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Yes, because we can sell his art and build his -- even though it's a monument for where people -- he wanted people to get married, it's a monument to his love of life.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Is this going to get built?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "At the time, he was thinking Las Vegas.", "docId": "120514pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Where will it go?", "qSentId": 617}]